Contact

mariposaceltica@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/carey-butler-27a67524 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing Healthcare ICU

Languages

Spanish (Professional Working) English (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

PALS BLS ACLS

Carey Butler

Intensive Care Nurse at LRS Healthcare

Nashville Metropolitan Area

Summary

ICU RN and Real Estate Agent. Experienced in the fields of insurance sales, transportation, defense and healthcare. It is my strong desire to improve life for all those so touch, whether in business or healthcare.

Medical Specialties: Adult ICU, Pediatric ICU, Adult and Pediatric Med/Surg, NICU, CVVH. Strong interest in holistic based therapies combined with Western Medicine.

Experience

LRS Healthcare
Intensive Care Nurse
June 2020 - Present (3 months)
Burlingame, California, United States

CVICU, Neuro ICU, Surgical ICU, MICU, PICU, House Float, Stepdown

HealthTrust Workforce Solutions Critical Care Travel RN August 2019 - Present (1 year 1 month) Marion, North Carolina

AMN Healthcare Travel Nurse March 2020 - June 2020 (4 months) Modesto, California, United States

Adult/Pediatric ICU, Neuro, Trauma, House Float

Ascension Critical Care Registered Nurse October 2018 - March 2020 (1 year 6 months) Nashville, Tennessee

Medical, Surgical and Cardiac ICU

Aspire Health, Inc.
Triage Nurse
May 2018 - October 2018 (6 months)
Nashville, Tennessee

Vanderbilt University Medical Center Trauma Critical Care RN September 2017 - May 2018 (9 months) Nashville, Tennessee

BaylorScottandWhite McKinney Registered Nurse - Float Pool September 2014 - November 2017 (3 years 3 months) McKinney, TX

Critical Care, Acute Care, NICU, and ED.

Children's Medical Center
Neuro/Trauma ICU RN
July 2009 - September 2014 (5 years 3 months)
Dallas/Fort Worth Area

Cares for all facets of traumas including traumatic brain injury, motor vehicle accidents, ingestions, various disease processes. Care of patients in Neuro/Trauma, NICU, PICU and CICU. Initiates and titrates vasoactive drips, actively monitors and interprets vital signs and follows protocol to maintain patient stability. Runs CVVH (dialysis), Administration of blood products, vasoactive medications, electrolytes and chemotherapeutic agents. Airway management, rapid transfuser, ventilated patients, cardiac caths, end of life and withdrawal care

SSM Health Care Registered Nurse January 2008 - July 2009 (1 year 7 months)

Provided care and administered daily medications to pediatric and geriatric populations.

- ◆ Addressed patient needs such as wound care, feeding and medication administration.
- ◆ Completed necessary paperwork, permits and charting from admission to discharge throughout the patient's stay.
- ♦ Notified physicians of changes in patient condition, or need for adjustment of medications. Escalated care as necessary.

♦ Trained and mentored new staff and participated in training videos.

Repeatedly received employee of the month recognition

Boeing

Office Administrator

October 2003 - October 2007 (4 years 1 month)

Bridgeton, Missouri

- ♦ Office Administrator support for Directors, Vice Presidents, Program Managers and support staff.
- ♦ Created presentations, spreadsheets, expense reports and arranged travel.
- ◆ Managed customer meetings with the US Navy, Air Force and other International customers.
- ◆ Implementation of meetings at multiple locations utilizing PowerPoint, Web-Ex, Video Teleconferences.
- ♦ Collaborated with HR, Quality and Engineering to provide spreadsheets and analysis to upper management.

Jackson Products, Inc Administrative Assistant August 2002 - March 2003 (8 months) Fenton, MO

Hussmann Assistant Export Manager May 2000 - August 2002 (2 years 4 months)

Bridgeton, MO

Enterprise Rent-A-Car Administrative Assistant to the V.P. of National Reservations January 1999 - May 2000 (1 year 5 months) Clayton, Missouri

Flexible Concepts Insurance Administrative Assistant July 1997 - October 1998 (1 year 4 months) Dallas, Texas

Assisted clients with resolution of claims issues. Maintained and prepared spreadsheets and sales presentations for large and small group health, life and dental proposals.

Education

Maryville University of Saint Louis
Bachelor of Science, Nursing · (2005 - 2007)

Kansas State University
Pre-Vet Med · (1992 - 1993)